<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release.xsd">
    <p xlink:href="/rest/p/piece_flow">Piece_Flow</p>
    <c>pear.piece-framework.com</c>
    <v>1.16.0</v>
    <st>stable</st>
    <l>BSD License (revised)</l>
    <m>iteman</m>
    <s>A web flow engine and continuation server</s>
    <d>Piece_Flow is a web flow engine and continuation server.

Piece_Flow provides a stateful programming model for developers, and high security for applications.</d>
    <da>2008-07-28 21:44:57</da>
    <n>A new release of Piece_Flow is now available.

What's New in Piece_Flow 1.16.0

 * Enhanced interfaces: getActiveFlowExecutionTicket() has been added to the Piece_Flow_Continuation_Service class. It can be used to get the flow execution ticket for the active flow execution. And also isViewState() has been added to the Piece_Flow class. It can be used to get whether the current state of a flow execution is a view state or not.
 * Improved error handling: The behavior of internal error handling has been changed so as to handle only own and &quot;exception&quot; level errors.
 * A defect fix: A defect that the outer frame of an already removed flow execution to be created by garbage collection has been fixed.

See the following release notes for details.

Enhancements
============

- Added getActiveFlowExecutionTicket() to get the flow execution ticket for the active flow execution. (Piece_Flow_Continuation_FlowExecution, Piece_Flow_Continuation_Service)
- Added isViewState() to get whether the current state of a flow execution is a view state or not. (Piece_Flow)
- Changed the behavior of internal error handling so as to handle only own and &quot;exception&quot; level errors.
- Replaced all uses of PIECE_FLOW_ERROR_FLOW_NAME_NOT_GIVEN with PIECE_FLOW_ERROR_FLOW_ID_NOT_GIVEN.
- Changed the behavior of internal error handling that an exception from Stagehand_FSM is always wrapped with Piece_Flow_Error::push().

Defect Fixes
============

- Fixed a defect that the outer frame of an already removed flow execution to be created by garbage collection. (Piece_Flow_Continuation_FlowExecution)</n>
    <f>59125</f>
    <g>http://pear.piece-framework.com/get/Piece_Flow-1.16.0</g>
    <x xlink:href="package.1.16.0.xml"/>
</r>