<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release.xsd">
    <p xlink:href="/rest/p/piece_unity">Piece_Unity</p>
    <c>pear.piece-framework.com</c>
    <v>0.11.0</v>
    <st>beta</st>
    <l>BSD License (revised)</l>
    <m>iteman</m>
    <s>A Web application framework</s>
    <d>Piece_Unity is a Web application framework.

Piece_Unity allows stateful programming without thinking about sessions by storing and restoring states with a technology known as continuation server. It also provides high security and eases the burden of implementing security measures for applications by application flow control.</d>
    <da>2007-02-19 20:51:55</da>
    <n>Hi all,

A new release of Piece_Unity is now available.

This release includes a feature named &quot;Fallback View&quot; which can be used for rendering a fallback view if an error occured while rendering with a specified view, and a feature named &quot;Plug-in Aliases&quot; which can be used multiple aliases as the name of a plug-in class by setting multiple prefixes.

Also this release includes a new plug-in &quot;ConfiguratorChain&quot; so that it can invoke multiple configurators. In the release after next, &quot;ConfiguratorChain&quot; will become the default configurator instead of &quot;KernelConfigurator&quot;.

And also other enhancements and two fixes are included. See the following release notes for details.

## Enhancements ##

### Kernel ###

##### Piece_Unity_Plugin_Factory #####

- Added a feature named &quot;Plug-in Aliases&quot; so that this feature can be used multiple aliases as the name of a plug-in class by setting multiple prefixes. (Ticket #40)

##### Piece_Unity_URL #####

- Added removeQueryString() to remove a name/value pair from the query string.

### Plug-ins ###

##### Renderer_Flexy, Renderer_HTML, Renderer_PHP, Renderer_Smarty #####

- Added a feature named &quot;Fallback View&quot;. (Ticket #37)
  If an error occured while rendering with a specified view and useFallback is true, a fallback view will be rendered.

##### KernelConfigurator #####

- Added a configuration point &quot;pluginPrefixes&quot; for using &quot;Plug-in Aliases&quot;.
- Added two configuration point &quot;validationValidatorPrefixes&quot; and &quot;validationFilterPrefixes&quot; for using &quot;Validator Aliases&quot; and &quot;Filter Aliases&quot;. (Ticket #43)

##### Renderer_Redirection #####

- Added a feature so that __eventNameKey is replaced with the event name key. (Ticket #38)

##### View #####

- Added a feature named &quot;Self Notation&quot; for redirection to an entry point itself. (Ticket #39)

##### ConfiguratorChain, Configurator_Env, Configurator_Event, Configurator_Plugin, Configurator_Request, Configurator_Validation #####

- Added a new plug-in &quot;ConfiguratorChain&quot; so that it can invoke multiple configurators. (Ticket #45)
  In the release after next, &quot;ConfiguratorChain&quot; will become the default configurator instead of &quot;KernelConfigurator&quot;.

### Example Applications ###

- Changed so as to use of ConfigurationChain.

## Defect Fixes ##

### Kernel ###

##### Piece_Unity_URL #####

- Fixed the problem so that EZweb mobile phone cannot redirect with Renderer_Redirection plug-in. (Ticket #44)

### Plug-ins ###

##### Renderer_Redirection #####

- Fixed the problem that the renderer cannot redirect to HTTPS URL.</n>
    <f>172906</f>
    <g>http://pear.piece-framework.com/get/Piece_Unity-0.11.0</g>
    <x xlink:href="package.0.11.0.xml"/>
</r>