<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release.xsd">
    <p xlink:href="/rest/p/piece_unity">Piece_Unity</p>
    <c>pear.piece-framework.com</c>
    <v>0.12.0</v>
    <st>beta</st>
    <l>BSD License (revised)</l>
    <m>iteman</m>
    <s>A Web application framework</s>
    <d>Piece_Unity is a Web application framework.

Piece_Unity allows stateful programming without thinking about sessions by storing and restoring states with a technology known as continuation server. It also provides high security and eases the burden of implementing security measures for applications by application flow control.</d>
    <da>2007-05-27 01:49:05</da>
    <n>A new release of Piece_Unity is now available.

What's New in Piece_Unity 0.12.0

 * Configurator_AppRoot plug-in: A plug-in for setting the directory and the URL path that form the top of the document tree of an application visible from the web.
 * Configurator_PieceORM plug-in: A plug-in for Piece_ORM.
 * Several defect fixes: A defect in fallback view rendering has been fixed. And also a defect in Plug-in Aliases has been fixed. And other defects have been fixed.

See the following release notes for details.

Enhancements
============ 

Plug-ins:

- Added the plugins_dir configuration point. (Renderer_Smarty)
- Updated &quot;Self Notation&quot; so as to set true to the configuration point &quot;addFlowExecutionTicket&quot; of Renderer_Redirection plug-in. (View)
- Added &quot;Configurator_PieceORM&quot; plug-in for Piece_ORM.
- Added &quot;Configurator_Proxy&quot; plug-in for proxy.
- Changed the default value for the configuration point &quot;configurator&quot; from &quot;KernelConfigurator&quot; to &quot;ConfiguratorChain&quot;. (Root)
- Added &quot;Configurator_AppRoot&quot; plug-in for setting the directory and the URL path that form the top of the document tree of an application visible from the web. (Ticket #56)
- Removed the configuration point &quot;importSessionIDFromRequest&quot;. (Interceptor_SessionStart)

Kernel:

- Updated pushPEARError() so that the params field in the repackage array contains &quot;userinfo&quot; and &quot;debuginfo&quot; fields, which contains each of the return values from getUserInfo() and getDebugInfo(). (Piece_Unity_Error)
- Updated the constructor so as to receive a prefix for determining the plug-in name. (Piece_Unity_Plugin_Common)
- Changed the error type on all Piece_Unity_Error::pushError() calls from &quot;warning&quot; to &quot;exception&quot;. (Piece_Unity_URL)
- Added getRemoteAddr() for getting an IP address (or IP addresses) of the client making the request. (Piece_Unity_Context)
- Added _getExtension()/_getConfiguration(). (Piece_Unity_Plugin_Common)
  getExtension()/getConfiguration() are deprecated since Piece_Unity 0.12.0. (Ticket #54)

Example Applications:

- Changed the function for URI encoding from escape() to encodeURIcomponent(). (ahah.js)
- Replaced all &quot;__basePath&quot; with &quot;__appRootPath&quot;.

Defect Fixes
============ 

Plug-ins:

- Fixed a defect in fallback view rendering that caused a fallback view to be always rendered in spite of success in HTML rendering if one or more &quot;warning&quot; level errors raised before rendering. (Ticket #57)

Kernel:

- Fixed the problem that a plug-in with Plug-in Aliases cannot get the current configuration. (Ticket #53)
- Fixed the problem that the getExtension()/getConfiguration() cannot work with an empty prefix. (Piece_Unity_Plugin_Common)

Example Applications:

- Fixed the problem that all radio elements are transferred regardless of whether they are checked or not. (ahah.js)</n>
    <f>177966</f>
    <g>http://pear.piece-framework.com/get/Piece_Unity-0.12.0</g>
    <x xlink:href="package.0.12.0.xml"/>
</r>