<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release.xsd">
    <p xlink:href="/rest/p/piece_unity">Piece_Unity</p>
    <c>pear.piece-framework.com</c>
    <v>1.0.0</v>
    <st>stable</st>
    <l>BSD License (revised)</l>
    <m>iteman</m>
    <s>A Web application framework</s>
    <d>Piece_Unity is a Web application framework.

Piece_Unity allows stateful programming without thinking about sessions by storing and restoring states with a technology known as continuation server. It also provides high security and eases the burden of implementing security measures for applications by application flow control.</d>
    <da>2007-07-18 20:16:23</da>
    <n>This is the first stable release of Piece_Unity.

What's New in Piece_Unity 1.0.0

 * Components: A component is a package that consists of plug-ins, services, GUI elements (HTML templates, images, scripts, etc.), flow definition files, action classes, and entry points, etc.. Many plug-ins are extracted as each Piece_Unity_Component_Xxx package. See the following release notes for details.
 * Services: A service is one or more classes that provides useful operations for client use.
 * The Piece_Unity_Service_FlowAction class: The Piece_Unity_Service_FlowAction class can be used as the base class for Piece_Flow actions.

See the following release notes for details.

Enhancements
============ 

Plug-ins:

- Added error handling. (Interceptor_SessionStart)
- Moved the process of preloading Dispatcher_Continuation plug-in from Configurator_Plugin to Interceptor_SessionStart.
- A improvement for restoring action instances in session. (Dispatcher_Continuation, Interceptor_SessionStart, Piece_Unity_Session_Preload)
- Changed the error type on all Piece_Unity_Error::pushError() calls from &quot;warning&quot; to &quot;exception&quot;. (ConfiguratorChain, InterceptorChain, OutputBufferStack)
- Moved the following plug-ins to components/. These plug-ins will be packaged as each Piece_Unity_Component_Xxx package.
  * Interceptor_Authentication
  * OutputFilter_ContentLength
  * Renderer_Flexy
  * Renderer_JSON
  * OutputFilter_JapaneseZ2H
  * KernelConfigurator (obsoleted)
  * Interceptor_NullByteAttackPreventation
  * Configurator_PieceORM
  * Interceptor_ProxyBasePath (obsoleted)
  * Renderer_Smarty

Services:

- Added the base class for Piece_Flow actions. (Piece_Unity_Service_FlowAction)

Kernel:

- Changed factory() to throw an exception if the configuration directory or the configuration file not found. (Ticket #66) (Piece_Unity_Config_Factory)
- Added a class loader. (Piece_Unity_ClassLoader)
- Updated an exception to be raised when an undefined extension point is used. (Ticket #72) (Piece_Unity_Plugin_Common)
- Updated getResults() so that a Piece_Right_Results object can be get by a validation set name. (Ticket #70) (Piece_Unity_Validation)
- Improved error handling so as to recognize the place where the exception is raised. (Piece_Unity_Plugin_Common)
- Added hasResults() to check whether or not the Piece_Right_Results object of the given validation set or the latest validation exists. (Piece_Unity_Validation)</n>
    <f>53898</f>
    <g>http://pear.piece-framework.com/get/Piece_Unity-1.0.0</g>
    <x xlink:href="package.1.0.0.xml"/>
</r>