<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release.xsd">
    <p xlink:href="/rest/p/piece_orm">Piece_ORM</p>
    <c>pear.piece-framework.com</c>
    <v>0.3.0</v>
    <st>beta</st>
    <l>BSD License (revised)</l>
    <m>iteman</m>
    <s>An object-relational mapping framework</s>
    <d>Piece_ORM is an object-relational mapping framework.

Piece_ORM is a simple framework based on the DataMapper pattern, and features stdClass centered approach.</d>
    <da>2007-05-19 17:24:06</da>
    <n>A new release of Piece_ORM is now available.

What's New in Piece_ORM 0.3.0

* getCount method: getCount() is used to get the number of rows a query would have returned without a LIMIT clause in the latest findAll method execution.
* findOneXxx methods: findOneXxx methods can be defined with arbitrary SQL queries to get the value from the first column of the first row of the result set.

See the following release notes for details.

Enhancements
============ 

Mappers:

- Added more strict quoting and removing unused properties when building a query.
- Added getCount() that is used to get the number of rows a query would have returned without a LIMIT clause in the latest findAll method execution. (Ticket #33)
- Added a feature that findOneXxx methods can be defined with arbitrary SQL queries to get the value from the first column of the first row of the result set. (Ticket #34)
- Added findOneWithQuery() to get the value from the first column of the first row of the result set with the given query.

Kernel:

- Changed the error type on all Piece_ORM_Error::pushError() calls from &quot;warning&quot; to &quot;exception&quot;.
- Updated setDatabase() to throw the same exception as getConfiguration(), getMapper(), etc. have been used.
- Removed code that avoided calling error handler.</n>
    <f>44227</f>
    <g>http://pear.piece-framework.com/get/Piece_ORM-0.3.0</g>
    <x xlink:href="package.0.3.0.xml"/>
</r>