<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2 http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2.xsd">
    <p xlink:href="/rest/p/piece_orm">Piece_ORM</p>
    <c>pear.piece-framework.com</c>
    <v>1.0.0</v>
    <a>0.3.0</a>
    <mp>4.3.0</mp>
    <st>stable</st>
    <l>BSD License (revised)</l>
    <m>iteman</m>
    <s>An object-relational mapping framework</s>
    <d>Piece_ORM is an object-relational mapping framework.

Piece_ORM is a simple framework based on the DataMapper pattern, and features stdClass centered approach.</d>
    <da>2008-04-20 04:26:24</da>
    <n>A new release of Piece_ORM is now available. This is the first stable release of Piece_ORM.

What's New in Piece_ORM 1.0.0

 * Automatic Timestamp: The current timestamp is set to the createdAt/updatedAt property automatically when insert/update if a table has a created_at/updated_at field.
 * Optimistic Locking: Optimistic Locking by the lock_version field has been supported only in default queries.
 * LOB support: The LOB support provides easy-to-use interfaces to handle LOBs using mappers.
 * Array support: Quotable (scalar or null) values in an array are expanded with a comma in a query.
 * the useMapperNameAsTableName option: If you want to use a mapper name as a table name, set the useMapperNameAsTableName option to true in the piece-orm-config.yaml.

See the following release notes for details.

Enhancements
============ 

- Added a feature so that quotable (scalar or null) values in an array are expanded with a comma in a query. (Piece_ORM_Mapper_Common)
- Added a built-in variable $__table which is replaced with an appropriate table name in mapper definition files. (Ticket #67) (Piece_ORM_Mapper_Common)
- Added a feature so as to use a mapper name as a table name by setting the useMapperNameAsTableName option to true in the piece-orm-config.yaml. (Ticket #71)
- Removed support for Identity Map.
- Changed factory() so as to use the given cache directory as is. (Ticket #58) (Piece_ORM_Config_Factory)
- Changed setConfigDirectory()/setCacheDirectory() to not return the previous value. (Ticket #56) (Piece_ORM_Mapper_Factory, Piece_ORM_Metadata_Factory)
- Added support for LOB.
- Added a feature so that a DBMS specific function to get the current timestamp is set to the createdAt/updatedAt property automatically when insert/update. (Ticket #81) (Piece_ORM_Mapper_Common)
- Added support for Optimistic Locking by the lock_version field only in default queries. (Ticket #84) (Piece_ORM_Mapper_Generator)</n>
    <f>94930</f>
    <g>http://pear.piece-framework.com/get/Piece_ORM-1.0.0</g>
    <x xlink:href="package.1.0.0.xml"/>
</r>